<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Hui Song's Homepage</title><link href="file:///Users/fafey/virtualenvs/pelican/homepage2/src/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="file:///Users/fafey/virtualenvs/pelican/homepage2/src/feeds/editorial.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>file:///Users/fafey/virtualenvs/pelican/homepage2/src/</id><updated>2012-09-11T11:21:00+02:00</updated><entry><title>Fursuiting in Las Vegas</title><link href="file:///Users/fafey/virtualenvs/pelican/homepage2/src/posts/2012/09/11/fursuit-page-live/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2012-09-11T11:21:00+02:00</updated><author><name>tBunnyMan</name></author><id>tag:file:///Users/fafey/virtualenvs/pelican/homepage2/src,2012-09-11:posts/2012/09/11/fursuit-page-live/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;I finally got around to knocking another big task off my list of things to do and sat down to do all the research and post up a full page of information on fursuiting in Las Vegas! Check along the top bar for the link to the new suiting research page!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's not complete by a long shot yet and it &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; needs your help. If &lt;strong&gt;you have fursuited publicly or semipublicly in the last year I really need your feedback&lt;/strong&gt; on different locations, problems you have encountered, and awesome business owners that were cool with you suiting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please leave comments in the post or send me an email so I can grow this into a great resource for all local suitors and suiters to be!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One thing I want the page to highlight, at least initially, is that we need to be aware of some of the laws being written and passed &lt;em&gt;right now&lt;/em&gt; concerning public performance. When fur suiting we are put into the same category as all other street performers in town and are subject to our laws. Earlier this year most of those laws were smashed because of some amazing court cases defending our first amendment rights but Oscar Goodman and others have made it clear they want to &lt;em&gt;heavily restrict&lt;/em&gt; the locations in which you can suit and possibly even require a permit on a per person basis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;P.S. Don't forget the con naming contest is still going on!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>theBunnyMan at RMFC2012</title><link href="file:///Users/fafey/virtualenvs/pelican/homepage2/src/posts/2012/08/11/off-to-rmfc/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2012-08-11T13:45:00+02:00</updated><author><name>tBunnyMan</name></author><id>tag:file:///Users/fafey/virtualenvs/pelican/homepage2/src,2012-08-11:posts/2012/08/11/off-to-rmfc/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hyias all!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are reading this it might be because I already talked to you at RMFC.
Thanks for visiting our page and looking into what Vegas Furry Arts is looking
to put on. If you have any questions, comments, or ideas &lt;em&gt;please&lt;/em&gt; check the 
contact page and send us a message.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you heard about this through a friend and are at RMFC please feel free to 
grab the guy with a HUGE bunny tail, long white ears, and a beard. It's probably 
theBunnyMan. If it isn't let him go before he gets mad, apologize and then go 
find the real Bunny Man. I'm more than happy to talk about what we are trying 
to accomplish and any experience or help you may be able to provide.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks,
 tBunnyMan&lt;/p&gt;</summary><category term="convention"></category></entry><entry><title>A fraternity by any other name</title><link href="file:///Users/fafey/virtualenvs/pelican/homepage2/src/posts/2012/07/17/membership2/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2012-07-17T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>tBunnyMan</name></author><id>tag:file:///Users/fafey/virtualenvs/pelican/homepage2/src,2012-07-17:posts/2012/07/17/membership2/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;I've been pondering over my earlier membership quarry a lot since I posted about it. Honestly that's my biggest holdup from whipping sheets off of this plan and putting together the committee. What kind of group is this really?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Public Club/Private Board&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This idea requires the least amount of work and on paper sounds like the best idea… yet I have watched it fail many times. All we do is find the steering committee that will run everything and then make everything that we run open to everyone. A public club with a fixed steering group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;VegasFurs.org worked like this for the 7 years that I ran the group and the simple fact is that this seems to create a large disconnect in the system. Usually the open attendees and members enjoy it but still feel a vague malcontent to their "overlords" running everything. Then the steering group becomes disenfranchised since they are the only ones putting the work into everything yet often end up resented for it. The few people who actually contribute become absorbed into the steering group and the fresh blood causes everything to revitalize up but over time the cycle continues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Original idea&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My original statement was that it's an art centric furry social club. We have open but listed and maintained membership with a board and driven purposeful goals. The question always was, does an open and free membership policy works with what we are trying to accomplish? &lt;em&gt;Maybe&lt;/em&gt;; I already discussed this in the last post. No one became a club member to go to AC or PawFur, however for quarterly or monthly meets it could be useful to keep everything purpose driven. My problem is that what does the maintained yet open membership differ from the public club/private board method? In fact last year when I turned over
VF and it became VF.net, in spirit this is what it changed to. The board is locked off until you sign up, which anyone can, and then you are a part of the group and everyone can go as long as you are in the group or are a +1…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But how is this different from the First idea? So far in practice it isn't different at all. It's totally the same except you can sit down and count people. In the end most of the membership isn't personally vested in the forward moment of the community. Usually if the group's open membership is older there is less of this since (in my experience), the older the base group is the higher percentage of contributors there are. Youth adds a lot of energy and spontaneity to the group but they usually have far less resources and will to commit to actual work. Youth just wants to do &lt;em&gt;something&lt;/em&gt; but Age tends to want to commit to stuff. In the end both are needed to keep a larger community flowing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maybe there is a way around this… to make the members more vested in the community by making a bigger deal about membership. However, the moment we start to put restrictions and goals and requirements to membership we stop being open membership and we become a fraternity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;The Fraternity&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When talking to another friend about this idea the concept of a Furry Fraternity keeps coming up. You join by committing yourself to the group, both with a time and fiscal responsibility, then you become a part of this group which is a social group unto itself. This method could help us stay more focused while keeping the membership net wide and making sure we have growth and "fill in" in the board. If we have at least somewhat open membership then we make sure the group doesn't end up running around with massive blinders. It allows us to be more than just a convention committee, which I also think is important.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is how V.A.G.I.N.A works and while it's a lot of administrative overhead it can indeed really blossom into amazing. However like V.A.G.I.N.A, Shriners, and other fraternities there is a lot of administrative overhead to it. You have to keep track of the group and keep it highly focused on it's goals and contributions to the community as a whole or it just devolves into a private clique. I already have close friends and I don't need to put in volunteer time and pay memberships to hang out with them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Refocusing&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;VFA isn't about doing things easy, it's about doing things right, learning from my 7+ years of group management and putting together something that can breath life into this massive furry community. Whole VF.net is still running strong I'm seeing a lot of fall off, especially in the older brackets where there isn't any fill. I want to put together events that &lt;em&gt;everyone&lt;/em&gt; wants to go to. I want to build a group that isn't exclusive, yet still fosters a level of closeness and community that other furry communities have, the kind that doesn't quarrel or fight with the rest of the furries in town but works with them to make things amazing… Oh and don't forget the art… it's kinda in the name… lets make something amazing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maybe some of this is a pipe dream. I probably can't have my cake and eat it too... but I'm gonna get close.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Membership vs open events</title><link href="file:///Users/fafey/virtualenvs/pelican/homepage2/src/posts/2012/07/12/membership/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2012-07-12T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>tBunnyMan</name></author><id>tag:file:///Users/fafey/virtualenvs/pelican/homepage2/src,2012-07-12:posts/2012/07/12/membership/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;I honestly don't know how to handle membership.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have minor ideas here and there but they are not fully formed. My inital though is that anyone that wants to go to an event should have to be a registered memeber and to have the fee be nothing. Then we can keep track of everything for liability reasons and all that. However that seems like it would be a fiasco when trying to acheve the main goal of the events. No one has to join a group to go to AC or PawFur.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So then do we only have staff? Just the people large enough to put on the event?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maybe we have a full membership with dues, and put on small events internally with fringe benifits like catering and cool stuff. Then the staff itself focuses the group towards working on the major big events. I think this is kind of how some cons work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've got ideas but not answers.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>My Goals</title><link href="file:///Users/fafey/virtualenvs/pelican/homepage2/src/posts/2012/07/11/goals/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2012-07-11T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>tBunnyMan</name></author><id>tag:file:///Users/fafey/virtualenvs/pelican/homepage2/src,2012-07-11:posts/2012/07/11/goals/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;I wanted  to sit and iterate over all my goals. If anything just to help look over what this group is designed for and maybe help some people understand what the big idea is by talking about the details a little.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;The main goal&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think the end goal, the main number one us to put on events for local furs that people want to go to. I know I can't make everyone happy but in my 7+ years of being a major player in the local furry community I often hear the same complaints over and over again when it comes to meets. For the 6 years I ran the boards I found that almost every complaint boiled down to one of the following;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;"It costs too much to go to amusement place X"&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;"I don't wanna eat at place X I just wanna hang out"&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Someone&lt;/em&gt; throw a house party cause I can't"&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;"The park is boring cause it's just everyone standing about"&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know there are other complaints like "Too many kids, My friends aren't here, ect" I can't grant every wish but I think I can cover the above list. The idea is to put on small events, in rented areas where we can fit everyone in together and have something for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Here is my "dream list";&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Small event space at far off-strip casino like the suncoast&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Whole event, one room, one day&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;LOW admission, sub 15$&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A small dealers corner like 5 heads&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Curtained off fur suit changing/decom area in the back&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Video-game area in a corner&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tabletop game area right by video games&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lots of tables for art and chilling&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A stage for some performances&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A few panels, all held on said stage, all art and fur suit construction stuff... maybe some comedy or games.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I would offer a catered lunch (for a fee)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An ice cream social (again for fee)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Things I wouldn't have;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Art show (I love them but I don't see the event being big enough to support one)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;GOH. Just no. If you wanna come, perform, or promote please do but not on the dime of the attendees.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A "con book". I'd print out two massive poster with all details and events and slap it on two walls.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An external charity. I know it's the "thing to do" but the goal is to provide an event with minimal cost to the attendee. The altruism here is to contribute to the Furry Arts Community, not PETA/Shelters/ASPCA. We are not looking at making a profit either though, just covering the costs. Anything over will be put into a treasury for the next event.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Speaking of money, anyone getting paid. Right, &lt;strong&gt;no one&lt;/strong&gt; affiliated with VFA gets paid, even a little. No reimbursements, no none of that. Money goes into FVA and &lt;em&gt;only&lt;/em&gt; goes out to pay other entities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;The bigger picture.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The bigger picture is that FVA can be a respectable social group internally as well as the committee that puts on these events. I'm personally not sure how much I want to drive this but once things come together I think the steering committee can help out these plans. I think my only big thing here is that I want administrative transparency. I think everyone is getting old of the private administrative groups where no one knows what they are doing, or talking about, or what is going on. I want people to know what we do and what we are discussing.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><category term="convention"></category></entry><entry><title>What inspired this?</title><link href="file:///Users/fafey/virtualenvs/pelican/homepage2/src/posts/2012/07/09/inspiration/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2012-07-09T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>tBunnyMan</name></author><id>tag:file:///Users/fafey/virtualenvs/pelican/homepage2/src,2012-07-09:posts/2012/07/09/inspiration/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;As this page grows and I talk to people about this I find the thing I have to explain the most is the motivation behind it. Of course people are going to ask the bunny man;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Why?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What do you want to accomplish here?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After the last time?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Why?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well the simple answer is because no matter what happens I will always be a furry for life. At 30+ years old I will never not be a furry. Not only that but I will always want to do great things with furry, bring people together, and help create the events and community meetings that I enjoy so much.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On some levels VFA is the evolution of what I imagined for VF: greymuzzles, a group that's not based on a forum, Facebook page, or really any other online medium. A group that is about creating events; Not just meet ups, events. Obviously we need some sort of direct online communication to set things up and notify people but that should be the ends to the means of putting together more events.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However GreyMuzzles just didn't pan out like that. It turned into a bunch of private parties I throw at my house at a regular basis and a bar meet that feels almost as exclusive. Don't get me wrong I &lt;em&gt;Love&lt;/em&gt; what GreyMuzzles is right now but it's not enough. It feels too exclusive. I want to do things that invite people in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then earlier this year I went to Paw Fur. I make no qualms about intentionally and grossly stealing the mass majority of this inspiration from Science, Inc, the group who put that on. They were not the online/regulars community but they worked with the local communities to make sure everyone was invited. They put on the best small event, and maybe the best furry event, I have ever seen with my own two eyes. It probably wasn't everything to everyone and some people may have hated it. The point though is that at 5$ and a Sunday of your time it was more than enough. There was easily 120 people that showed up and there was stuff to do with them besides mill around, but most importantly it was &lt;em&gt;for the locals&lt;/em&gt;. So many con idea's I see for Las Vegas are NEVER about the locals. Its all about some group that wants another Las Vegas vacation. I'm all for attracting in out of town friends and giving people an excuse to come out but why should we be putting on conventions for the tourists? We already support the Strip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since then ideas have been chumming around in my head. Why couldn't we do something like that &lt;em&gt;quarterly&lt;/em&gt; even? Focus on growing Las Vegas' community internally and let &lt;em&gt;that&lt;/em&gt; draw in whoever wants to come out? Well, there was lots of smaller things standing in the way. Over the next months though little things started to fall into place. Eventually someone told me the solution to several of my biggest problems and then this idea really took off. I tried pitching similar idea's about in the admin of VF.net but it never took off. No one was interested in running such an ordeal. If I offer you the job and you don't want it I'm gonna do it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Obviously, as of this writing I'm not done planning. I'm just rambling to a site that only a rare few people know about in hopes that I can put together a really solid plan we can take off the ground.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What do you want to accomplish here?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the tersest terms possible I want to create a regular by locals for locals mini-con exactly like &lt;a href="http://www.pawfur.com/"&gt;PawFur&lt;/a&gt;. Now that isn't the whole story, that's just the end game.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In order to get there I want to assemble a steering group that is community/forum/group agnostic. I want us to focus purely on creating more than just meet ups. I want to create events where we can focus on furry art. I don't mean drawing either. I mean on the art of furries and maybe even the art of being a furry in a sense. I'm talking about painting, writing, fur suiting, cooking, music; Hell, if you have taken playing blazeblue to an art form then lets embrace it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What about what happened last time?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, this isn't VegasFurs.org, it's not meant to replace VegasFurs.org, and honestly I only see a gauge difference between trying to corral together a forum of people and keep the drama and fighting down while still trying to provide as open environment as possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the biggest hindsight flaws I thing there was with the way I set it up is that VF.org didn't scale. Once the group got too big it was too much for anyone, or small group, to manage. Especially because it tried to be everything. Forum, Chat, Meeting co-ordinator, problem mediator; it was just too much! There is so much minutia drama and issues to deal with and not enough reliable structure in place to handle this. FVA will have a listed and official steering group that will act as a team to  handle all issues in a well thought out professional manner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The goal with FVA is simple and to the point. FVA exists solely to create furry themed events, each with its own purpose and goals based around enrichment of the arts for Southern Nevada furs. It sounds a bit more preachy than it will likely turn out but you gotta strive for excellence.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry></feed>