<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Hui Song's Homepage</title><link href="file:///Users/fafey/virtualenvs/pelican/homepage2/src/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="file:///Users/fafey/virtualenvs/pelican/homepage2/src/feeds/grocery.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>file:///Users/fafey/virtualenvs/pelican/homepage2/src/</id><updated>2012-09-11T11:21:00+02:00</updated><entry><title>Fursuiting in Las Vegas</title><link href="file:///Users/fafey/virtualenvs/pelican/homepage2/src/posts/2012/09/11/fursuit-page-live/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2012-09-11T11:21:00+02:00</updated><author><name>tBunnyMan</name></author><id>tag:file:///Users/fafey/virtualenvs/pelican/homepage2/src,2012-09-11:posts/2012/09/11/fursuit-page-live/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;I finally got around to knocking another big task off my list of things to do and sat down to do all the research and post up a full page of information on fursuiting in Las Vegas! Check along the top bar for the link to the new suiting research page!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's not complete by a long shot yet and it &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; needs your help. If &lt;strong&gt;you have fursuited publicly or semipublicly in the last year I really need your feedback&lt;/strong&gt; on different locations, problems you have encountered, and awesome business owners that were cool with you suiting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please leave comments in the post or send me an email so I can grow this into a great resource for all local suitors and suiters to be!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One thing I want the page to highlight, at least initially, is that we need to be aware of some of the laws being written and passed &lt;em&gt;right now&lt;/em&gt; concerning public performance. When fur suiting we are put into the same category as all other street performers in town and are subject to our laws. Earlier this year most of those laws were smashed because of some amazing court cases defending our first amendment rights but Oscar Goodman and others have made it clear they want to &lt;em&gt;heavily restrict&lt;/em&gt; the locations in which you can suit and possibly even require a permit on a per person basis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;P.S. Don't forget the con naming contest is still going on!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>What inspired this?</title><link href="file:///Users/fafey/virtualenvs/pelican/homepage2/src/posts/2012/07/09/inspiration/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2012-07-09T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>tBunnyMan</name></author><id>tag:file:///Users/fafey/virtualenvs/pelican/homepage2/src,2012-07-09:posts/2012/07/09/inspiration/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;As this page grows and I talk to people about this I find the thing I have to explain the most is the motivation behind it. Of course people are going to ask the bunny man;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Why?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What do you want to accomplish here?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After the last time?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Why?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well the simple answer is because no matter what happens I will always be a furry for life. At 30+ years old I will never not be a furry. Not only that but I will always want to do great things with furry, bring people together, and help create the events and community meetings that I enjoy so much.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On some levels VFA is the evolution of what I imagined for VF: greymuzzles, a group that's not based on a forum, Facebook page, or really any other online medium. A group that is about creating events; Not just meet ups, events. Obviously we need some sort of direct online communication to set things up and notify people but that should be the ends to the means of putting together more events.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However GreyMuzzles just didn't pan out like that. It turned into a bunch of private parties I throw at my house at a regular basis and a bar meet that feels almost as exclusive. Don't get me wrong I &lt;em&gt;Love&lt;/em&gt; what GreyMuzzles is right now but it's not enough. It feels too exclusive. I want to do things that invite people in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then earlier this year I went to Paw Fur. I make no qualms about intentionally and grossly stealing the mass majority of this inspiration from Science, Inc, the group who put that on. They were not the online/regulars community but they worked with the local communities to make sure everyone was invited. They put on the best small event, and maybe the best furry event, I have ever seen with my own two eyes. It probably wasn't everything to everyone and some people may have hated it. The point though is that at 5$ and a Sunday of your time it was more than enough. There was easily 120 people that showed up and there was stuff to do with them besides mill around, but most importantly it was &lt;em&gt;for the locals&lt;/em&gt;. So many con idea's I see for Las Vegas are NEVER about the locals. Its all about some group that wants another Las Vegas vacation. I'm all for attracting in out of town friends and giving people an excuse to come out but why should we be putting on conventions for the tourists? We already support the Strip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since then ideas have been chumming around in my head. Why couldn't we do something like that &lt;em&gt;quarterly&lt;/em&gt; even? Focus on growing Las Vegas' community internally and let &lt;em&gt;that&lt;/em&gt; draw in whoever wants to come out? Well, there was lots of smaller things standing in the way. Over the next months though little things started to fall into place. Eventually someone told me the solution to several of my biggest problems and then this idea really took off. I tried pitching similar idea's about in the admin of VF.net but it never took off. No one was interested in running such an ordeal. If I offer you the job and you don't want it I'm gonna do it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Obviously, as of this writing I'm not done planning. I'm just rambling to a site that only a rare few people know about in hopes that I can put together a really solid plan we can take off the ground.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What do you want to accomplish here?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the tersest terms possible I want to create a regular by locals for locals mini-con exactly like &lt;a href="http://www.pawfur.com/"&gt;PawFur&lt;/a&gt;. Now that isn't the whole story, that's just the end game.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In order to get there I want to assemble a steering group that is community/forum/group agnostic. I want us to focus purely on creating more than just meet ups. I want to create events where we can focus on furry art. I don't mean drawing either. I mean on the art of furries and maybe even the art of being a furry in a sense. I'm talking about painting, writing, fur suiting, cooking, music; Hell, if you have taken playing blazeblue to an art form then lets embrace it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What about what happened last time?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, this isn't VegasFurs.org, it's not meant to replace VegasFurs.org, and honestly I only see a gauge difference between trying to corral together a forum of people and keep the drama and fighting down while still trying to provide as open environment as possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the biggest hindsight flaws I thing there was with the way I set it up is that VF.org didn't scale. Once the group got too big it was too much for anyone, or small group, to manage. Especially because it tried to be everything. Forum, Chat, Meeting co-ordinator, problem mediator; it was just too much! There is so much minutia drama and issues to deal with and not enough reliable structure in place to handle this. FVA will have a listed and official steering group that will act as a team to  handle all issues in a well thought out professional manner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The goal with FVA is simple and to the point. FVA exists solely to create furry themed events, each with its own purpose and goals based around enrichment of the arts for Southern Nevada furs. It sounds a bit more preachy than it will likely turn out but you gotta strive for excellence.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry></feed>